{
    "subject": "resource/RATP_Group",
    "predicate": "property/locationCountry",
    "object": "France",
    "human_readable": "RATP Group is located in France.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9224401712417603,
            "question": "Does the RATP Group primarily function in France?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8848187923431396,
            "question": "Where is the RATP Group located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6388416290283203,
            "question": "In which country does the RATP Group operate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5007123947143555,
            "question": "What type of organization is the RATP Group?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44074758887290955,
            "question": "Are there any other countries where the RATP Group has operations?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3796612620353699,
            "question": "What is the main purpose of the RATP Group?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3503318428993225,
            "question": "Is the RATP Group a public or private organization?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3186233937740326,
            "question": "What services or industries might the RATP Group be involved in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.24265296757221222,
            "question": "Can you give an example of a service provided by the RATP Group?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.16945631802082062,
            "question": "Does the RATP Group have any international partnerships?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=RATP Group is located in France.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5932_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you give an example of a service provided by the RATP Group?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5932_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What services or industries might the RATP Group be involved in?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5932_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is the RATP Group a public or private organization?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5932_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5932_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5932_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5932_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5932_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5932_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5932_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5932_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5932_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5932_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5932_87.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, here's the evaluation of the triple:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe documents mention that \"The RATP Group is international public transport developer and operator headquartered in Paris, France.\" (from file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_5932/re-ranker-msmarco/87.txt) and also state that \"RATP is headquartered in Paris, France.\" (from file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_5932/re-ranker-msmarco/43.txt). This information supports the triple that RATP Group is located in France."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents mention that the RATP Group is headquartered in Paris, France, and operates in numerous countries including France. Therefore, it supports the statement that the RATP Group is located in France."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}